costumecity.com 2011-11-05

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy Effective: 4.6.09**

The Costume City Inc. is a Participant in the TRUSTe Privacy Seal Program. TRUSTe is an independent organization whose mission is to advance privacy and trust in the networked world. As this Web site (www.costumecity.com) wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices monitored for compliance by TRUSTe. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact us at [service@costumecity.com](mailto:service1@CostumeCity.Com). If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry, or if your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe at http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php. TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve your concerns. 

At Costume City, we are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to process orders and to provide a more personalized shopping experience. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.

**Tell-A-Friend**  
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. Our server will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. 

You may also send an email to a third party via the located on each page of the site. This widget allows a user to type in an email address and provides the capability to send a link with a message. Costume City Inc. does not harvest emails given and they are discarded when the user closes their browser session.

**Reviews**  
If you post a review on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other readers of these reviews, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.  
  
**What Information Do We Collect? How Do We Use It?**  
When you order, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit-card number and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your orders and to notify you of your order status. 

You may voluntarily sign up to be informed about certain offers. For this service we need only an e-mail address, which we use to send the information you requested. 

When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, we may ask for your name, address and e-mail address, so we can administer the contest and notify winners. 

We personalize your shopping experience by using your purchases to shape our recommendations about other merchandise that might be of interest to you. We also monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage to help us develop the design and layout of the store. 

We may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important changes to the Web site, new Costume City services and special offers we think you'll find valuable. If you would rather not receive this information, please notify us. Make sure to notify us for each account or e-mail address you have left with us. 

**Service Providers**  
Credit card transactions are facilitated via Yahoo Store and PayPal. Costume City is the owner of the data entered on the Yahoo Store pages and this information is subject to the privacy policies of www.costumecity.com. If you wish to use PayPal to purchase a product on our Site, you will be taken to the PayPal Site to complete your transaction. We use a third party shipping service to send orders to customers and Live Chat to handle online customer service requests. 

**How Does Costume City Protect Customer Information?**  
We have taken every precaution to make your transactions secure. When you use your credit card to shop at CostumeCity.Com, the transaction is safe and will be stored on our secure server up to 30 days to process payments and/or refunds only. 

Our servers use industry-standard security measures, including SSL (Secure Sockets Layer), an advanced encryption technology. This technology safeguards your personal information and guarantees privacy.

**Legal Disclosure**  
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, warrant, subpoena, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

**Access to your personal information**  
If you wish to change, update or delete any of the information you have knowingly provided to the site, please email us Ops@CostumeCity.Com and we will facilitate your request. 

**Will Costume City Disclose the Information it Collects to Outside Parties?** ****  
Costume City does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others. We may choose to do so in the future with trustworthy third parties, but you can tell us not to by sending a blank e-mail message to [ops@CostumeCity.Com](mailto:Ops@CostumeCity.Com). (If you use more than one e-mail address to shop with us, send this message from each e-mail account you use.) 

Also, Costume City may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics are purely aggregate in nature and will not include personally identifying information.

** Cookies**  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited.

We use a third-party tracking service that uses cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate

**In Summary**   
We are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to make shopping at CostumeCity.Com possible and to enhance your overall shopping experience. 

**Links to Other Sites**  
This web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by CostumeCity.Com. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site.

**Your Consent**  
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by CostumeCity.Com. If we decide to make material changes to our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page and prominently on the homepage so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

**Tell Us What You Think**  
CostumeCity.Com welcomes your questions and comments about privacy.  
Please e-mail us at [Ops@CostumeCity.Com](mailto:Ops@CostumeCity.Com).

CostumeCity.Com  
641 Strander Blvd.  
Tukwila WA 98188
